mobilestopic.com 2011-02-20

# Privacy Policy, Mobile Phone News : MobilesTopic.com

### Privacy Policy

#### [MobilesTopic.com](http://www.mobilestopic.com/ "Best mobile phone resource") is committed to protecting your privacy.

At **MobilesTopic.com** we work hard to personally review and test all hosting companies listed on our site. We are also constantly updating the information we provide to ensure that it is current. However, we are not responsible for any mistakes, omissions or misinformation that might occur, including personal experiences with those companies.  

#### What information do we collect? 

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our website users unless it is voluntarily supplied to us. When users visit our websites, they may choose to join our newsletters. Only those who provide us with personally identifiable information will be able to receive newsletters. The information we collect include a name and an e-mail address.  

#### How do we use the information?

We use the information you provide us to provide our users with updates and information regarding the various products that we review, new products and technologies that enter the marketplace, and notifications of new review sites that we create. **We will never sell, trade, or otherwise give away any personal information that we collect.**  

#### Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Thank you for visiting our site.  
Sincerely, 

#### MobilesTopic.com
